/**
 * Created by David Snawder on 8/2/2016.
 */
var quiz1 = [ {
    theQuestion: "In the TV series Firefly, what is the name of the main crew's ship?",
    choices: ["Firefly","Star Cruiser","Serenity","Persephone"],
    answer: 2
}, {
    theQuestion: "Which character says the line 'I am a leaf on the wind - watch how I soar'?",
    choices: ["Wash", "Malcolm", "Inara", "Zoe"],
    answer: 0
}, {
    theQuestion: "What is the film companion to the show?",
    choices: ["Firefly: The Movie","Star Cruiser","Serenity","Trick question, there's no film."],
    answer: 2
}, {
    theQuestion: "How many episodes did the show last before it was canceled?",
    choices: ["22","18","12","14"],
    answer: 3
}
];

var quiz2 = [{
    theQuestion: "The Resident Evil series goes by a different title in Japan. What is it?",
    choices: ["Infection","Biohazard","Virus","Evil Residence"],
    answer: 1
}, {
    theQuestion: "Jill Valentine and Chris Redfield are members of Raccoon City Police Department's special task force S.T.A.R.S. What does S.T.A.R.S. stand for?",
    choices: ["Special Tactics and Reconnaissance Service","Strike Team and Rescue Service","Super Talented and Really Sexy","Special Tactics and Rescue Service"],
    answer: 3
}, {
    theQuestion: "What is the name of the mansion in which the game takes place?",
    choices: ["Spencer Mansion", "Arklay Mansion", "Oswell Mansion", "Birkin Mansion"],
    answer: 0
}, {
    theQuestion: "What is the date shown in the game's opening sequence on which the events take place?",
    choices: ["June 1998","July 1997","July 1998","June 1997"],
    answer: 2
}
];

var quiz3 = [{
    theQuestion: "I am born in fear, raised in truth, and I come to my own in deed. Where I'm called forth, I serve the cause of need. What am I?",
    choices: ["Respect","Courage","A king","Lava"],
    answer: 1
}, {
    theQuestion: "Anyone can hold me, even without their hands, but no one can do it for long. What am I?",
    choices: ["Bladder", "Breath", "Tongue", "Lava"],
    answer: 1
}, {
    theQuestion: "When you do not know what I am, then I am something. But when you know what I am, then I am nothing. What am I?",
    choices: ["A tale","Lava","A riddle","A disappointing announcement"],
    answer: 2
}, {
    theQuestion: "The rich want it, and the poor have it; it is greater than God, but worse than Satan; and if you eat it you will die. What is it?",
    choices: ["Happiness","A grudge","Hot lava","Nothing"],
    answer: 3
}
];

